Lesson 22. Susan shares the good news. Bob tells Susan that the village market won't take their cookies anymore.
Susan tells Bob that the national cookie company wants to buy out Susan's scrumptious cookies.
Dear, I've got some bad news.
What's the matter, Bob?
The village market won't take any more of our cookies.
Why not? They're selling like hotcakes.
I know, but a lady found a blue hair in her cookie. Now Carol refuses to sell them.
Carol is such a dragon lady. We're better off having nothing to do with her.
She's not my cup of tea either, but she was selling lots of cookies.
Oh well, that's the way the cookie crumbles. Ha ha, get it?
Susan, this is no laughing matter.
Bob, we don't need the village market anymore. Why not?
The national cookie company called. They want to buy out our business.
Susan, this is a dream come true. It looks like we've struck it rich.
Yes, soon we'll be rolling in dough.